# **KENNETH ANDALES**

### FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER



keanolida7296@gmail.com

Allen, Northern Samar

kenneth-andales.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/kenneth-andales

# SKILLS

HTML
CSS
SASS
JS
TS
PHP
BOOTSTRAP
TAILWIND
JQUERY
REACT
CODEIGNITER
LARAVEL
EXPRESS
MYSQL
MONGODB

# KNOWLEDGE

OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING
DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM
SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION
SINGLE PAGE APPLICATION
MODEL VIEW CONTROLLER
FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT
AUTHENTICATION TOKEN
ALGORITHM CODING
REST API

### EDUCATION

**BS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY** 

Palawan State University 2013 - 2018

### PROFILE

With 2 years of web development experience,

I am dedicated to staying up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies. I am eager to work on diverse projects and collaborate with other developers to improve my knowledge and skills. I approach every project with enthusiasm and attention to detail, striving to deliver high-quality code that meets client needs.

### EXPERIENCE

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER (Partime)

Bluehive Ph - Quezon City, Metro Manila - Wfh August 2022 - September 2022

Managed front-end development and collaborated with the back-end development and project manager for various projects. My responsibilities included API integration and providing daily and weekly updates on project progress.

#### FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER (Freelance)

WerOrg - Florida, USA - Wfh January 2022 - April - 2022

Successfully rebuilt the back-end application of an e-commerce site, adding translation capabilities and fixing minor onboarding issues. Additionally, I addressed some SEO-related issues on a live website. As part of my responsibilities, I handled the cPanel to upload code changes.

### **SOFTWARE DEVEOPER**

Cloud Panda Phils Inc. - BGC Taguig, Metro Manila October 2019 - March 2020

Collaborated with other developers to build both government and internal websites. Additionally, I worked with QA testers to fix bugs in other projects. My responsibilities included uploading code to Bitbucket and updating the status of tasks on our project management tool.

#### JR. WEB DEVELOPER

International Payment Processing - PPC, Palawan May 2018 - April 2019

Collaborated with junior and senior developers as well as my supervisor on minor or major tasks. Additionally, I managed to build a solo project with some assistance from other developers.